http://www.woodcocksmokery.com/privacy-policy

The Keep
Why Work With Wild?
The Keep
Why Work With Wild?
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Contact
Woodcock Smokery Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy sets out how Woodcock Smokery uses and
protects any information that you give Woodcock Smokery when you use
this website.Woodcock Smokery is committed to ensuring that your
privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information
by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be
assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy
statement.Woodcock Smokery may change this policy from time to
time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time
to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective
from 21 May 2018.What we collectWe may collect the following information:• name and job title• contact information including email address• demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests• other information relevant to customer servicesWhat we do with the information we gatherWe
require this information to understand your needs and provide you with
an effective service, and in particular for the following reasons:• Internal record keeping. • We may use the information to improve our products and services. •
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special
offers or other information which we think you may find interesting
using the email address which you have provided. • From time to
time, we may also use your information to contact you for market
research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We
may use the information to customise the website according to your
interests.Controlling your personal informationYou may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:•
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the
box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information
to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes.• if you have
previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct
marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by contacting
us. We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal
information to third parties unless we have your permission or are
required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send
you promotional information about third parties which we think you may
find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.You
may request details of personal information which we hold about you
under the Data Protection Act 1998. If you would like a copy of the
information held on you, please contact us.When requesting
information, you should also include any additional details that would
help to locate your data - for example, a customer account number or
email address used for your account. You may be asked for evidence of
your identity. This is to make sure that personal information is not
given to the wrong person. If you believe that any information
we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us as
soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be
incorrect.SecurityWe are committed to ensuring that
your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or
disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and
managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect
online. How we use cookiesA cookie is a
small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard
drive. Once you agree, the file is added, and the cookie helps analyse
web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies
allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web
application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes
by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We
use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This
helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in
order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for
statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the
system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better
website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which
you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any
information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You
can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers
automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser
setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from
taking full advantage of the website.Links to other websitesOur website may
contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used
these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any
control over these other websites. Therefore, we cannot be responsible
for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide
whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this
privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy
statement applicable to the website in question.
If you are interested in booking private courses on a date of your choosing, please contact sally@woodcocksmokery.comAll fish is wild, with no colourants or artificial nonsense, using only salt and hardwood smoke. How it has always been preserved over the millenia before the mass industrialisation and commodification of nature’s precious and beautiful resources.Photography and web design by MAX JONES @uptherethelast
